<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fragment-Andrioid-Kotlin</string>

    <string name="sachin">Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar is a former Indian international cricketer and a former captain of the
        Indian national team, regarded as one of the greatest batsman of all time. He is the highest run scorer of all
        time in International cricket.
    </string>
    <string name="sourav">Sourav Chandidas Ganguly, affectionately known as Dada, is a former Indian cricketer and
        captain of the Indian national team, Currently, he is appointed as the President of the Cricket Association of
        Bengal and President of the Editorial Board with Wisden India
    </string>
    <string name="virendra">Virender Sehwag is a former Indian cricketer. Widely regarded as one of the most destructive
        batsmen of all time, Sehwag played as an aggressive right-handed opening batsman and also bowled part-time
        right-arm off-spin. He played his first One Day International in 1999 and joined the Indian test side in 2001
    </string>
    <string name="virat">Virat Kohli is an Indian international cricketer who currently captains the India national
        team. A right-handed top-order batsman, Kohli is regarded as one of the best batsmen in the world. He plays for
        Royal Challengers Bangalore in the Indian Premier League, and has been the team\'s captain since 2013.
    </string>
    <string name="yuvraj">Yuvraj Singh is an Indian international cricketer, who plays all forms of the game. An
        all-rounder who bats left-handed in the middle order and bowls slow left-arm orthodox, Yuvraj is the son of
        former Indian fast bowler and Punjabi actor Yograj Singh.
    </string>
    <string name="ajay">Ajaysinhji \"Ajay\" Jadeja, is a former India cricketer, who had been a regular member in the
        Indian cricket team between 1992 and 2000. He played 15 Test matches and 196 One Day Internationals for India.
        His cricketing achievements were overshadowed by a 5-year ban for match-fixing.
    </string>
    <string name="dhoni">Mahendra Singh Dhoni is an Indian international cricketer who captained the Indian national
        team in limited
    </string>
    <string name="sachin_image">
        https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/25/Sachin_Tendulkar_at_MRF_Promotion_Event.jpg
    </string>
    <string name="sourav_image">
        https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e8/Sourav_Ganguly_closeup.jpg/520px-Sourav_Ganguly_closeup.jpg
    </string>
    <string name="ajay_image">
        https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/b/bb/Ajay_jadega.jpg/520px-Ajay_jadega.jpg
    </string>
    <string name="virat_image">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e4/Virat..Kohli.jpg</string>
    <string name="virendra_image">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Virendra_sehwag_72.jpg</string>
    <string name="yuvraj_image">
        https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Yuvraj_Singh_appointed_as_Ulysse_Nardin_watch_brand_ambassador.jpeg
    </string>
    <string name="dhoni_image">
        https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/Mahendra_Singh_Dhoni_January_2016_%28cropped%29.jpg
    </string>


</resources>
